In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the OH as in NO diphthong.
我们将学习如何发音 OH，如 NO 中的双元音。
Diphthongs are a combination of two sounds.
双元音是两个音的组合。
They have a starting position and an ending position.
它们有一个起始位置和一个结束位置。
The jaw drops for the beginning position,
下巴在起始位置时下垂，
tongue shifts back a little bit.
舌头稍微向后移动。
The lips may start relaxed or may start rounding right from the beginning.
嘴唇可能从一开始就放松，或者从一开始就开始圆润。
After dropping the jaw,
下巴下垂后，
immediately start moving into the ending position.
立即开始移动到结束位置。
The lips round, and the back part of the tongue stretches up.
嘴唇变圆，舌头的后部向上伸展。
Focus on the movement of the jaw and the lip rounding.
专注于下巴的运动和嘴唇的圆润。
Let's see this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个声音。
Jaw drop for the first position,
下巴下垂到第一个位置，
and rounded lips for the second.
第二个位置嘴唇圆润。
The word slow.
单词 slow。
Notice how the lips are not relaxed in the first position of this diphthong with the jaw drop.
注意在这个双元音的第一个位置下巴下垂时，嘴唇并不放松。
They're flared, which does not affect the sound,
它们是张开的，这并不影响声音，
as they prepare to round for the ending position.
因为它们准备在结束位置变圆。
Rounded lips.
嘴唇圆润。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the OH diphthong curves up, then down.
OH 双元音先上升，然后下降。
Slow.
Slow。
OH.
OH。
In an unstressed syllable,
在非重读音节中，
it's lower and flatter in pitch,
音调更低更平，
as well as quieter and quicker.
而且更安静更快。
OH.
OH。
The diphthong is unstressed in the word OK.
在单词 OK 中，双元音是非重读的。
OH.
OH。
Let's take a look at the word OK.
让我们看看单词 OK。
The jaw drops,
下巴下垂，
but not quite as much as it did on the stressed syllable of slow.
但没有像在 slow 的重读音节中那样多。
The lips begin to round for the transition into the ending position.
嘴唇开始圆润，为过渡到结束位置做准备。
The lips round, but not quite as much as for the stressed OH in slow.
嘴唇变圆，但没有像在 slow 中的重读 OH 那样多。
Here we compare the first position of the stressed OH on top with the unstressed version on the bottom.
这里我们比较重读 OH 的第一个位置在上面，非重读版本在下面。
Less jaw drop for the unstressed version.
非重读版本的下巴下垂较少。
And here, the second position.
这里是第二个位置。
You can see that for the stressed OH on top, the lips round more than they do in the unstressed version.
你可以看到在上面的重读 OH 中，嘴唇比在非重读版本中更圆。
Generally,
通常，
the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong is more relaxed,
非重读版本的元音或双元音更放松，
and often doesn't take the full mouth position.
通常不需要完整的口腔位置。
In this case,
在这种情况下，
less jaw drop and less lip rounding.
下巴下垂和嘴唇圆润较少。
This is because we don't take as much time for unstressed syllables.
这是因为我们在非重读音节上花费的时间较少。
They're shorter.
它们更短。
So we simplify the mouth movements.
所以我们简化了口腔动作。
The OH diphthong, stressed.
OH 双元音，重读。
Slow.
Slow。
OH.
OH。
Unstressed.
非重读。
OK.
OK。
OH.
OH。
Window.
Window。
OH.
OH。
Window.
Window。
Phone.
Phone。
OH.
OH。
Phone.
Phone。
Social.
Social。
OH.
OH。
Social.
Social。